[Music] Hi there,
[Música]
what's up family? Nice to
muy buenas Qué pasa familia encantado de
be here with you again another day in
estar aquí con ustedes otro día más en
another video this time I have to
otro videito en esta ocasión tengo que
tell you about some tweets that I just saw
comentaros unos tweets que acabo de ver
from my colleague Diego Arrabal that I
del compañero Diego arrabal que
sincerely think are going to be quite a
sinceramente Creo que van a dar bastante
talk throughout the week. I don't know if he
que hablar durante la semana no sé si lo
did it on purpose to provoke and I
ha hecho a propósito para provocar y
don't want to jump in and get ahead of myself in
tampoco me quiero lanzar Y adelantar
case I misinterpret them.
vaya a ser que yo los interprete mal en
First of all, well, I have to warn you that with
primer lugar bueno tengo que avisar que
respect to the program that
respecto al programa que hicimos ayer
Marina and I did yesterday, well, there have been all kinds of
Marina y yo pues ha habido todo tipo de
reactions. There are no programs in which
reacciones no hay programas en los que a
maybe the next day the atmosphere
lo mejor al día siguiente el ambiente
is more heated and this program
está más caldeado y este programa de
last night, well, it seems to be
ayer por la noche pues parece que está
getting a lot of talk and there are people who did
dando bastante que hablar y hay gente a
n't like it. Okay, I'm not
la que no le ha sentado bien vale no lo
saying this about Diego specifically because I
digo por Diego en concreto porque
still don't know his interpretation, but I have
todavía no sé su interpretación pero sí
seen on other channels how there
que he visto en otros canales como
were even colleagues asking for it not to be seen, I
incluso había compañeros pidiendo que no
mean, I really don't understand
se viera o sea realmente no entiendo por
why there are people who were worried that
qué hay que estaban preocupados de que
people would want to see our program
la gente quisieran Ver Nuestro programa
or not. I mean, don't watch it, no, don't
o no O sea que no lo vieran no no lo
watch it, don't watch it. After that, they will probably
veáis no lo veáis ya después seguramente
publish clips of the best moments on Twitter.
en Twitter publiquen clip de los mejores
well it's better that you watch that so why watch the
momentos pues mejor que veáis eso para
whole thing? Why watch two
que verlo entero no Para qué ver las dos
hours? Hey, sorry, are you scared, do you have
horas oye perdona tienes algún miedo
a problem or something's wrong with you?
tienes algún problema o te pasa algo
Create a program that's the same or similar and they
crea tú un programa igual o parecido y
'll see you, it's okay, don't get
Te verán a ti no pasa nada no te pongas
nervous, it's not a problem either. No, and
nervioso que tampoco pasa nada no y
well, Diego arrabal. Well, he also
bueno Diego arrabal Pues también ha
wanted to give his opinion on the subject. There is
querido dar su opinión sobre el tema hay
part of Diego's community that is
parte de la comunidad de Diego que está
coming to tell me that if Diego
viniendo a decirme que si es que Diego
already gave that information, which I know is not true. Let's
ya dio esa información que se que no es
see, let's take it step by step, let's go step by step,
A ver vamos por partes vamos a ir por
calm down and we'll comment on it,
parte tranquilo y lo vamos a comentar
everything is worth it. Before continuing with the
todo vale antes de continuar con el
video, I ask you all to please
vídeo pediros a todos por favor que os
subscribe to the channel, it's completely
suscribáis al canal es completamente
free and if you give me a like and
gratuito y si me regaláis un like y
give your opinion in the comments box, I
opináis en la caja de comentarios os
will be eternally grateful to see
estaré Eternamente agradecido a ver el
yesterday's program with Marina, like
programa de ayer mío con Marina como
almost everyone else. I
casi todos
'm putting the "almost" being generous
estoy poniendo el casi siendo generoso
because I think they are all
porque yo creo que todos son una
wonderful, I mean, but wonderful.
maravilla o sea pero una maravilla yo
Every time I finish the program, I'm
cada vez que termino el programa me
left with a very good taste in my mouth. What a
quedo con muy buen sabor de boca Qué
good chat I have, what complicity, what about what, which one,
buena charla que hago qué complicidad
no, and
que qué tal qué cuál no y el programa de
yesterday's program was a bomb, I mean, Marina was
ayer fue una bomba o sea Marina estaba
responding to  Marta risk that Marta
respondiendo a Marta riesgo que Marta
ariesco has already become a participant in
ariesco ya se ha hecho participe de
fact, that is, at the time that Marta
hecho o sea en el momento que a mí Marta
risked me Because there are many people who say
arriesgó Porque hay mucha gente que dice
Oh but it's that Marta ariesco called her
Ay pero es que Marta arriesgo la llamó
privately Well but it's that Marta 10
por privado Bueno pero es que Marta 10
with the moment that she calls me to
con el momento que me llama a mí para
give me her version and that I have it and that
darme su versión y que yo la tenga y que
I can give it through her own words the other
yo la pueda dar por boca de ella el otro
day when I was in the snow kill
día cuando estaba yo en la nieve matar
disc is a participant Marta ricos has not
disco es partícipe Marta ricos no ha
entered the program yet because of the
entrado todavía en el programa por la
situation that you have otherwise she would have
situación que tienes sino ella hubiera
picked up the phone and entered
cogido el teléfono y hubiera entrado
too okay And yesterday does not
también vale Y ayer
come to mind either If at
tampoco se me viene a la cabeza Si en
some point we talk about exclu
algún momento hablamos de exclu
or super exclusive information that
o información súper exclusiva que no
nobody knows what I remember that yesterday it was
sepa nadie a mí lo que me suena que ayer
announced that it was going to be said was What did
se anunció que se iba a decir era A qué
Marina mean with that information
se refería Marina con esas informaciones
that Marta said She is lucky
que Marta dijo Tiene suerte
that many people around her do
que mucha gente de su entorno del
not go into telling it in
alrededor pues no entre en contarla
detail okay In fact I remember
detalladamente vale De hecho me suena
remembering to correct myself if I'm wrong that
recordar corregirme si me equivoco que
Marina on several occasions at the beginning
Marina en varias ocasiones al principio
of the program said Well there are many people
del programa dijo Bueno hay mucha gente
in the chat who more or less know things
en el chat que más o menos conoce cosas
that are not going to  surprise and such okay It
que no se van a sorprender y tal vale
turns out that there are things that Diego
Resulta ser que hay cosas que Diego
Arrabal had said in his in his
arrabal había dicho en su en sus
live shows and so on okay the problem with it
directos y demás vale el problema con lo
and I say this in a constructive way
y esto lo digo de manera constructiva de
really I don't say it in a negative way
verdad que no lo digo de manera negativa
or as a mean criticism or
ni como una crítica con mala leche ni
anything like that the problem with what
nada por el estilo el problema de lo que
often happens with
pasa muchas veces con los directos de
Diego Arrabal's live shows is that out of three hours
Diego arrabal es que de las tres horas
two are two and a half are music He for
dos son dos y media son música El por
some music promising whatever is in
una música prometiendo lo que ponga en
the title and that's it Well and those two and a
el título y ya Bueno y esas dos horas y
half hours with the music well they go
media pues con la música pues van
calling ladies at 806 and such that if it
llamando señoras al 806 y tal que si a
works for him it seems perfect to me I mean
él le funciona a mí me parece perfecto O
I'm not anyone to tell anyone
sea yo no soy nadie para decirle a nadie
How to run your channel the thing is that
Cómo llevar su canal la cuestión es que
many times they
muchas veces
are Bombs or it is the information that
son Bombas o son las informaciones que
the title promises and there were other times
prometen el título y había otras veces
when he has clicked a little bit with all the
que ha pinchado un poquillo con todo el
affection there have been other occasions that
cariño ha habido otras ocasiones que
well the information It has been a
bueno la información Se ha quedado un
little bit like that So what is happening well there
poquillo así Asa qué es lo que pasa pues
are things that go unnoticed
que hay cosas que pasan desapercibido
many times and then what
muchas veces y entonces lo que dijo
Diego said was the following that we are going to
Diego fue lo siguiente que vamos a
listen to next that is
escuchar a continuación que sí que es
part of what he said  Marina but
una parte de lo que dijo Marina pero
man, with all due respect, you're not going to
hombre a ver con todo respeto no me vais
compare me. But anyway, let's listen to
a comparar Pero bueno vamos a escuchar
what Diego said.
lo que dijo Diego
Marta, risk, has taken the reins of
Marta riesgo ha tomado las riendas
absolutely everything. When I say
absolutamente de todo Cuando digo de
everything, it's everything, everything, everything, Antonio
todo es de todo de todo de todo Antonio
David Flores, everything, everything, and that's what they let me know,
David flores todo todo todo y así me lo
and if it's not like that, let them
hacen llegar y si no es así
tell me otherwise, and I'll
que me digan lo contrario y yo ya les
tell them the following:
pondré lo siguiente
Antonio David, for several weeks now
Antonio David desde hace varias semanas
[Music] has been
[Música]
under,
está bajo
what are you going to call them, and under the
cómo va a llamarlos y bajo la
risk wand, and
varita de riesgo y se entendería la
Juan the editor's departure to the Channel would be understood. This would make
salida de Juan el editor al Canal así se
sense of what happened two weeks ago
entendería lo que pasó hace dos semanas
at the birthday party.
en el cumpleaños
This would make sense of so many, many,
así se entendería tantas y tantas y
many things that are happening and that will
tantas cosas que están pasando y que van
continue to happen.
a seguir pasando
Marta
Marta
is the leading voice there right now, I'm
es la voz cantante ahí ahora mismo yo ya
not getting involved, whether she's doing well or
no me meto si lo está haciendo bien o lo
doing badly, I'm not getting involved,
está haciendo mal yo ahí ya no me meto
they'll know, but Antonio David
ellos sabrán pero Antonio David
doesn't
no
[Music]
[Música]
either I don't want to give my opinion or I don't want to give my opinion,
o no quiero opinar o no quiero opinar
but everything that's being done there is
pero todo lo que se está haciendo ahí
going through,
pasa por
in short, okay, this whole issue of
en resumen vale todo el tema este de que
the family being worried because
la familia está preocupada porque
Antonio David gets carried away a lot and
Antonio David se deja llevar mucho y
all the decisions are made by Marta and
todas las decisiones las toma Marta y
Marta  symphony Marta Edge Marta the other one
Marta symphony Marta Edge Marta al otro
okay Yes but man let's see
vale Sí pero hombre a ver
that a lot of people are coming to me to say
que me esté viniendo mucha gente a decir
that everything I said yesterday Marina
que todo lo que digo ayer Marina ya lo
had already said Diego man let's see with all
habían dicho Diego hombre a ver con todo
the love eh And with all the respect to
el cariño eh Y con todo el respeto al
Diego's work but man it's not worth it
trabajo de Diego pero hombre no vale
balance of yesterday my conversation with Marina
saldo de ayer la charla mía con Marina
was headline after headline that if she
fue titular tras titular que si se
showed
presentaba en sálvame diciendo que era
up on Slvame saying that she was the e of Benzema that she called her teammates to tell him Hey today you have Caleta Are you going to talk about me or what if she rejects survivor because she doesn't trust that later when they return things won't be the same anyway no With all the respect with all
en fin no Con todo el respeto con todo
the love But it's not worth it Likewise it was not
el cariño Pero no vale Igualmente
promised as something that
tampoco se prometió como algo que no
nobody knew a secret that only
supiera nadie un secreto que solamente
came from Marina it was an
venía por parte de Marina era una
answer because Marina the other day
respuesta porque Marina el otro día dejó
dropped some things and it has been answered period
caer unas cosas y se ha respondido punto
Regarding the 30 Diego put okay And I'm
Respecto a los 30 ha puesto Diego vale Y
going to clarify it here because there are
voy a aclararlo aquí porque hay mucha
also many people who are throwing it in
gente también que se lo está echando en
Marina's face Diego has put I'm not
cara Marina Diego ha puesto no estoy
saying that this is a circus that
diciendo que esto es un circo que Había
Once upon a time there was a circus that always gladdened the
una vez un circo que alegraba siempre el
heart in  well I don't know if she's
corazón en fin no sé si está
joking and I don't know if I don't know for real I do
cachondeando y no sé si no sé de verdad
n't know How to interpret this because I
no sé Cómo interpretar esto porque
don't want to say anything other than what it is
tampoco quiero decir una cosa que no sea
but if it's because of the way the
pero si es por la forma de llevar el
program is carried out, of extending it or the outline No, that's
programa de alargarlo o la escaleta No
not Marina's fault that's
eso Marina no tiene la culpa eso es cosa
my thing because you already know how I carry out the
mía porque ya sabéis como yo llevo los
live shows and how I carry the program
directos y como yo llevo el programa
okay the program lasts two hours and I
vale el programa dura dos horas y yo
try to distribute it so that all two
intento repartir para que todas las dos
hours are entertaining Okay then apart from that I
horas sean entretenidas Vale entonces
want all the information to
aparte quiero que toda la información
be very clear and I was driving
quede muy claro y yo iba conduciendo
Well look Marina started here
Pues mira Marina ha empezado por aquí
Let's give it context here I'm going to
Vamos a darle contexto por acá te voy a
put this video now everything starts
poner este vídeo ahora todo empieza por
here
aquí
also telling her the part that
contándole también la parte que me había
Marta had told me so that she would answer me
dicho Marta para que ella me contestara
to what Marta had told me as if
a lo que me había dicho Marta como si le
Marta herself were answering her
estuviera contestando la propia Marta
directly no and then come on
directamente no y ya luego pues venga
Marina tell us everything you know but
Marina cuenta todos sabes pero
obviously I think
evidentemente yo creo que son
the two hours are unmissable but well I
imperdibles las dos horas pero bueno yo
hope
espero
I hope that this is not a complaint or
yo espero que esto no sea una queja o
a criticism of the way the
una crítica a la forma de estirar El
live show is stretched out the way it's carried out because you
directo a la forma de llevarlo porque me
're going to allow me but in my
vais a permitir pero en mi opinión
personal opinion there is neither  a minute of yesterday's live broadcast,
personal no hay ni un minuto del directo
okay, the information is
de ayer que vale que la información está
at this point, the other information
en este punto que la otra información
is at this minute, the other one, there isn't
está en este minuto que la otra no hay
a single minute of yesterday's live broadcast that is
ni un minuto del directo ayer que sea
unmissable. So, whatever it
imperdible
is, no, it's unmissable, okay, you
O sea que sea no que sea perdible vale
understood me, family. What do
me habéis entendido familia Qué pensáis
you think? How do you interpret these
ustedes cómo interpretáis estas
insinuations? I'll be reading the
insinuaciones os estaré leyendo la caja
comments box. We'll be waiting to see
de comentarios estaremos pendiente a ver
what others say and the overall
de lo que dicen los demás y de toda la
reception this talk is having.
recepción que está teniendo esta charla
A huge hug and until the next
un abrazo enorme y hasta el siguiente
video.
vídeo
[Music]
[Música]